Five years ago, there was a massive fire in Tengu City.
It mainly broke out in a small neighborhood called Nanko.
And that's when I first saw her.
The day she burned my parents alive.
If it's that easy for me to lose control over myself,
I wouldn't be shocked if I already have killed someone.
We'll never know what happened unless Kotari and I both get our memories back.
And until then...
Eventually her power will be too much.
I don't think she'll last longer than two days.
Only one person can save her.
I won't let her die.
His younger sister is a spirit.
He has a friend who is in the AST.
And somehow, Shiro must save them all.
The hero is a spirit.
And somehow, Shiro will notify me of her home.
The space is alive.
光求めた瞳
譲るのは絶望だけ
誰にも届かない叫び
探すその手で止めて
何もかも壊れた世界で
訳もわからないままに
触れた優しさがまだ怖くて
肌の空いた心の隙間
埋めてくれる人は君など
選んでてたら
お疲れ様に見たら
聞いたら
今朝は
お疲れ様でした
でも、一日のお疲れ様に
自分が生きている
お疲れ様にも
学校は休止してくれたら
それよりも時間がかかる
ごめんなさい
お疲れ様でした
そして、それにも
それにもお疲れ様でした
お疲れ様でした
と思います
2까지です
サイカ朝に
それ、ton期も
ワンサイズが
なるほど
の Carr ideology
で、
ふたやつの
データ
パブリック
マウェレ主な
聴が
皆さんの
玩闘が
どうやって
arrange some training for you before the date what training bring it on whatever
it takes to save coterie I'm ready for real
is there some kind of hidden message here how was shopping for swimsuits
training me look coterie's fate is on the line here I'm not gonna get the strike okay
train me can you believe how beautiful these are is every one of them called a
mizuki yeah in Japanese but what is it I mean what are you supposed to do with
you really don't know okay this is military zapped ultimate grind instrument mizuki for
short it's a new anti-spirit annihilation suit when it's activated the built-in
realizer starts the critical driving force and the warhead is broken into its
molecular components and discharged it easily cuts through spirit armor and it
destroys the target's body so that it can never be returned to its original
state what's wrong with you oh look permit what are you doing here what do you want
from us is it true did you bring us here to buy us annihilation suits no she's
making no I'm not he knows all about the mizuki and he's afraid he wants to
destroy you that's why you're here he was only trying to distract you so it would
be easier to make his attack I don't believe you Chido would never do
something like that to us she's lying right Chido no origami is telling the
truth I've been trying to figure out an easy way to kill you guys for weeks but
why I don't understand didn't say that she did
why you little coward Chido wasn't saying those things you were just playing a
trick on me I have no clue what you're talking about kind of a weird
coincidence running into you here oh hey how's your injury oh I'm all right
however it's not a coincidence I'm glad I got to see you Chido but Toka is
actually the one I'm here to talk to today talk about what some stuff do you
remember the spirit wearing flames that came down from the sky yesterday I know
you saw her I would like you to tell me what you remember even if I did know
something you're the last person I would tell pretty please with cherries stop
that what do you think you're trying to do I want you to tell me what you know
about the flame spirit pretty please all right I'll tell you but you have to pick
your head up it's confusing yes I did see the flame spirit she was I don't know very red
anything else let me think she was also very strong and is that it um I was like whoa when I saw
her that doesn't help me oh really you're bothering me for an explanation and now it's not good enough
for you by the way Shido I just realized the only swimsuit I have is the one from
the school swim team and what that means is it will become quite problematic later
if we decide to go to the beach or the pool oh okay well why don't you just buy
one while you're here problem solved I could but it's very important to get a
second opinion when choosing such things having a male opinion is especially
helpful I said having a male opinion is helpful well very helpful so are you just
trying to get me to check you now listen up origami if you want to play that way fine then
whoever excites Shido the most will win a date with him do you really want to waste your time I'll never
let you go on a date with him I will win what's happening why am I suddenly in the middle of a wet
t-shirt contest let's go with it this will be a good training exercise for you oh my gosh is that
Shido uh why is he hanging out in the girls swimwear section that's so lame and so it begins I hate it
let's look for something else we could try the school swimsuit that's so lame wow your heart
rates through the roof record-breaking numbers looks like those girls hey that is not funny I'm
trying I'm sorry to keep you waiting yes wonderful choice the simple design beautifully highlights
Toka's wholesome curves making her unwittingly arousing good girl so what do you think tell me
does it excite you at all what yeah yay I'll try something else then this was just a warm-up it gets
better how's this
what destructive power she has lovely contrast of dark fabric on pearl skin an updo with a string
halter is always a sassy choice fierce ah so what do you think me right I think it fits it looks nice
on you what do you think about this one yeah that's what I'm screaming about a knotty body combined with a
bashful modesty irresistible over here oh no what is she thinking ha does this mean you're giving up I
don't blame you take it off what I'm pretty sure you're not playing by the rules
and the game just took a surprising turn origami is stimulating him with the art of teasing less is
more one glimpse and his heart rate has gone through the roof imagination for the win
so what I still have more in me this isn't over yet
um cheeto will you come here I um I need your help
I'm here I'm coming in you're not hurt are you
I was trying to get it all by myself but it's hard to do with just one hand
looks like we have a winner game over
crap I don't ever want to go through that again I can't say I understand but at least you had some
entertaining commentary right did it help much better to see those girls there than during a date
so do you feel like you could handle it now for sure I'm completely focused on saving coterie
tomorrow it's on I won't let her down it's just that I wish I could remember you know what happened
five years ago how did I do it if I knew how I sealed her powers maybe this would be easier
there is one thing we might do to jog your memory would you like to look at the footage of the fire
from five years ago you have that
the flames are spreading quickly hot winds are blowing upward
this is lost aerial footage from one of the networks it was never aired
Rattatisker covered it up pretty well okay yes here it is
that's me in coterie wow now pay close attention
pause it wait why what did you see is there something I'm missing I don't see any movement
over there who is that or what is that on screen what are you talking about behind her
it's so blurry strange that I can still see a person through all that
hey what's wrong are you okay
sorry about last night clearly I did more harm than good by showing you that footage
oh don't worry about it I want to find out what that image was
but another time I gotta focus on this date
understood we're ready to help anytime you need it
so have faith in yourself today I have to say I've never seen a more talented playboy
no spirit stands a chance against your charm
thanks
all right coterie has just been sent to the ground
she should be arriving very soon you got this
roger that
hey there you are yep sorry for the wait
isn't there something else you'd like to say to me like about the outfit
I'm pretty sure that's the first thing we taught you
yes you did you look great is that for me
oh well not completely I mean it's not unusual for me to dress up to go out
but I also had to do something that would let you feel like it's an actual date
and compliments are nice every once in a while
all right come on let's get this date thing started
okay
yeah let's
oh boy we're gonna have so much fun
what's going on what are you guys doing here
oh guess I forgot to tell you
the girls will be accompanying you two on your date
we decided that would be a better plan in the long run
so group date huh
I love surprises how very brave
I can't wait to see how this turns out
Shito look
I brought the swimsuit you bought yesterday
the one you loved so much
yeah I brought mine too
hmm
you all went swimsuit shopping
how sweet
ah
this is so amazing
I can't believe they actually have a mountain and a lake inside the building
there's a lot of water here
I'm so excited I can't wait to swim
look another lake
can we go swim in that one please
sure but stay close
I can't wait
let's go Yoshino
okay
they sure have a lot of energy
so what's the deal here
you're checking out your sister now
of course not
don't be gross
you're about to compliment her
right
she dressed up for you today
coterie
that's my name
so yeah
that swimsuit
it uh
looks very nice of you
I mean you look cute
right on schedule
thank you Shito
was it Reina or Kanazuki
who told you to say that
neither
I mean it
yeah
well then I'm flattered
and
I'd love to know
what you like the most
about my look
everyone
your options are there
in front of you
so make your picks
hmm
those are all
fairly reasonable
option one
is a given
you can't go wrong there
not number two
because that sounds like
it's all about the suit
and not her
and three is just
asking for it
you're right about that
good point
option three
quick
I really love the way
your boobs
fill out the top
what did you just say to me
nothing I said
you're felt like a mob
what the hell
why is everyone freaked out
oh so suddenly
it's wrong to have
a great wreck
can you hear yourself
it's like you want
to dig for hot springs again
hey Shito
let's go on that
you want to try
the water slide
yeah
I bet all four of us
could ride together
oh it's okay
I don't want you
Shinon to get wet again
and I'm way too busy
being not five
so I'm out
oh darn
guess it's just you
and me then
this will be so fun
you're right
I changed my mind
I want to go
that's much better
thank you Toka
I wish Koturi would relax
and have fun on the date
but this doesn't surprise me
is there another way to ride
I mean
are you sure we're
you know
safe
not really
so hold on tight
that was the best ride ever
oh big bro
you okay
what's wrong
look
over there
can you get my ribbons
it was like
woo
and then
you are way too wild
for me
your ribbons are black
I just noticed that
there any special reason
why
do they look that bad
of course not
I was just curious
fine
I'll tell you
nosy
white is a vulnerable color
and today
I needed to be strong
black is strong
yum
this is so good
yes it is
thank you
you're welcome
glad you like it
hey Reyna
what's the reading
on Koturi's happiness meter
she looks pissed
it's not going down
but it's not going up either
there's been no change
so that means
she hasn't had
any fun at all
no way I can
seal her powers
like this
are you okay
yeah
just went down
the wrong pipe
I guess
hold on a sec
where are you going
I'm going to use
the restroom mother
not that it's
any of your business
any other girl
would have killed you
for asking
what'd I do
I just
I thought you and Koturi
we're getting along again
are you guys in a fight
it seemed like she was
mad at you
you look so relieved
when she stormed out of here
it's funny how easy
to read you are
huh
I'm that obvious
I need the restroom too
Reyna
can you tell
how freaked out
I am
what are my mental
readings right now
am I that easy
to read
hey Shido
it's me
I'm sorry
but Reyna
isn't here
to do the analysis
that's weird
where did she go
no
don't go over there
does that feel
any better
yes
much better
thank you
that was a close one
wasn't it
one more please
I don't want to risk
injecting more
I already gave you
50 times the normal dosage
I don't want to kill you
you really think
something like that
could kill me
drugs don't have
a very strong effect
in spirit mode
but
it would help
the date with Shido
I mean
with big bro
please Reyna
I know it's risky
but this might be
my last chance
to see him
if it fails
I won't be myself
anymore after today
but no matter
how it turns out
I want to be able
to finish my date
with him
be honest with me
how long has Coterie
been in that state
since the moment
she got her spirit
powers back
why didn't you tell me
Coterie wanted it
that way
she asked me not to
say anything to you
about it
she didn't want you
to spend your date
feeling sorry for her
if you want to help
pretend that you
didn't see any of this
Coterie will appreciate it
yeah I will
thank you
hey
where'd the girls go
I don't know
but I think you and I
should get dressed
and go to the amusement park
huh
you got orders
from Fraxinus
didn't you
it's not going well
out there
so you might want to
take her to ride
some rides indoors
whatever
not like it'll make
any difference
you're wrong
why'd you do that
I just like the amusement
park better than the pool
and I'm ready to leave
really
we don't have to take
Toka and Yoshino
they're having a blast
on the jungle cruise
are you ready
you haven't been here
in a while
so prepare to have
your mind blown
this is the equipment
that's right
it's an experimental
annihilation suit
DW-029
or white licorice
it has the firepower
of an entire
AST troop
in one monstrous unit
all it would take
is one shot
do you think
it would be possible
to even defeat
Ifrit using this
well if our simulations
are accurate
this baby holds enough power
to take down a spirit
but that doesn't mean
that you're allowed
to use it
you don't have the ability
or the authorization
a specialist wizard
from DEM
was crippled
after using it
on full power
for only 30 minutes
the first time
wait
why are you talking
about Ifrit
oh
I get it
the spirit
in the footage
was her
right
it's true
there were flames
what footage
I knew it was you
There was no cœur
you
and Manson
being
no
See you next time.